{
    "dialog_0": {
        "dialog": [
            {
                "turn_num": 0,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_0",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_0",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_0",
                "answer": "answer_0"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 1,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_1",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_1",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_1",
                "answer": "answer_1"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 2,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_2",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_2",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_2",
                "answer": "answer_2"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 3,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_3",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_3",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_3",
                "answer": "answer_3"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 4,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_4",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_4",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_4",
                "answer": "answer_4"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 5,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_5",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_5",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_5",
                "answer": "answer_5"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 6,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_6",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_6",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_6",
                "answer": "answer_6"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 7,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_7",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_7",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_7",
                "answer": "answer_7"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 8,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_8",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_8",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_8",
                "answer": "answer_8"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 9,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_9",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_0_9",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_0_9",
                "answer": "answer_9"
            }
        ],
        "annotator_name": null,
        "annotations": [
            {
                "turn_num": 1,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_1",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 2,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_2",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 3,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_3",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 4,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_4",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 5,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_5",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 6,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_6",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 7,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_7",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 8,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_8",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 9,
                "turn_id": "dialog_0_turn_9",
                "requires rewrite": null
            }
        ]
    },
    "dialog_1": {
        "dialog": [
            {
                "turn_num": 0,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_0",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_0",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_0",
                "answer": "answer_0"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 1,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_1",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_1",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_1",
                "answer": "answer_1"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 2,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_2",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_2",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_2",
                "answer": "answer_2"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 3,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_3",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_3",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_3",
                "answer": "answer_3"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 4,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_4",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_4",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_4",
                "answer": "answer_4"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 5,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_5",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_5",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_5",
                "answer": "answer_5"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 6,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_6",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_6",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_6",
                "answer": "answer_6"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 7,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_7",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_7",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_7",
                "answer": "answer_7"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 8,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_8",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_8",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_8",
                "answer": "answer_8"
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 9,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_9",
                "original_question": "question_dialog_1_1_9",
                "original_question_id": "question_id_1_9",
                "answer": "answer_9"
            }
        ],
        "annotator_name": null,
        "annotations": [
            {
                "turn_num": 1,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_1",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 2,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_2",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 3,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_3",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 4,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_4",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 5,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_5",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 6,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_6",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 7,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_7",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 8,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_8",
                "requires rewrite": null
            },
            {
                "turn_num": 9,
                "turn_id": "dialog_1_turn_9",
                "requires rewrite": null
            }
        ]
    }
}